She only has two desires, and one of them is justice.
Honey Don't! is a comedy, crime film directed by Ethan Coen.
Honey O'Donahue, a small-town private investigator, delves into a
series of strange deaths tied to a mysterious church.
Honey O'Donahue, played by Margaret Qualley.
MG Falcone, played by Aubrey Plaza.
Reverend Drew Devlin, played by Chris Evans.
Chère, played by Lera Abova.
Hector, played by Jacnier.
Spider (Honey’s Assistant), played by Gabby Beans.
Honey Don't!
is a 2025 neo-noir black comedy film directed by Ethan Coen, who
co-wrote the screenplay with his wife Tricia Cooke.
It is the second in a "lesbian B-movie trilogy" following
Coen and Cooke's Drive-Away Dolls (2024).
The film stars Margaret Qualley, Aubrey Plaza, Chris Evans, and Charlie Day.
Its world premiere was at the Midnight Screenings section of
the 2025 Cannes Film Festival on May 24, 2025.
It was theatrically released in the United States and
Canada by Focus Features on August 22, 2025.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of small town, drug trafficking,
dark comedy, private investigator, church.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.